Guide to the Robert L. Patten academic papers, 1963-2015 MS 410
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series VI: Addenda
  - Subseries D: Rice-Related
    - GSA Alcohol Policies (folder 2/2) (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - GSA history (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - GSA space (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Graduate students orientation, 1998-2003 (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Graduate Studies, 2007 (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Graduate travel policy, 2005-2006 (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Honor Council/Faculty Council, 2003 (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - HRC Mellon Seminar, 2010 (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - Huxley Symposium, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Job coordinator, 2006-2009 (Box 78, Folder 12)
    - Job search, 2007 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Kermode, Frank - seminar, c. 1995-1997 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Lieberman, Susan - Leadership Rice (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Library Committee, 1999-2003 (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Marathon Readings, 2008 (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - Marshals Committee, 2004-2008 (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - Master of the Graduate House - Year End Reports, 1992-1995 (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - McKillop Endowment, 2001-2003 (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - MLS, 2008 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Norelco Transcriber purchase, 1971 (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - PACs, 2005-2008 (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Pinsky Lecture Series, 2004-2005 (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Prizes, 2005-2007 (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Rapoport Prize, 2007 (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Renaissance appoinment, 1992-1993 (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Resarch assistants, 2005-2009 (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - Reynolds, Sally - course, 2004 (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - Rice Ally program - training materials (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - Rice Associates, 1999 (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - RFB, 2006-2008 (Box 79, Folder 20)
    - Rice Honor System (Box 79, Folder 21)
    - Rice Memorial Center 50th Year Anniversary Celebration, 2008 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Rice Merger (Baylor), 2009-2010 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Rice Research Grants, 1970-1977, 1996 (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Rice University Council, 1978-1998 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - Rice University Press, 2006 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Robert Lowry Patten Awards, 2005 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Robert Lowry Patten Fund, 2006-2008 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Romantics Search, 2003 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Romantics Search Committee - Bohrer, Martha (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Romantics Search Committee - Fang, Karen (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Romantics Search Committee - Frey, Anne (Box 80, Folder 11)
    - Romantics Search Committee - Goldsmith, J. Nathaniel (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Romantics Search Committee - Hacker, William (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Romantics Search Committee - Khalip, Jacques (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Romantics Search Committee - Mazzeo, Tilar (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Romantics Search Committee - Mulrooney, Jonathan (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - Romantics Search Committee - Rovee, Christopher (Box 81, Folder 2)
    - Romantics Search Committee - Sachs, Jonathan (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - Romantics Search Committee - Sharma, Sanjay (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Romantics Search Committee - Tontiplaphol, Betsy (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - SAFER, 2007-2008 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Saslav collection, 2001-2005 (Box 81, Folder 7)
    - School of Humanities groundbreaking, 1998 (Box 81, Folder 8)
    - Shepherd School of Music recital brochures, 2001 (Box 81, Folder 9)
    - Student Academic Ethics, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 10)
    - Student Association, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 11)
    - Teaching Assistants, 2005-2009 (Box 81, Folder 12)
    - Third Semester Review - academic probation, 2005-2008 (Box 81, Folder 13)
    - Travel funds, 1993, 2001-2002 (Box 81, Folder 14)
    - Travel grants, 2006 (Box 81, Folder 15)
    - Undergraduate Committee, 1996-2004 (Box 81, Folder 16)
    - Valhalla renovation, 1998-1999 (Box 81, Folder 17)
    - WIP talks (Box 81, Folder 18)
  - Subseries E: Academic Organizations
    - Adelphi University, NEH Grant Consultancy, 1996-1997 (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - AAAH (American Association for the Advancement of the Humanities), 1977-1978 (Box 82, Folder 2)
    - American Society for Eighteenth-Century Studies annual meeting, Montreal, 2006 (Box 82, Folder 3)
    - Banned Books Week, 2004-2006 (Box 82, Folder 4)
    - Browne/Lester materials, 2008-2009 (Box 82, Folder 5)
    - Cambridge University Press - Dickens in Context, 2006 (Box 82, Folder 6)
    - CELJ - Distinguished Editor Award (Box 82, Folder 7)
    - CELJ - E-Journals (Box 82, Folder 8)
    - CELJ - Judging E-Journals (Box 82, Folder 9)
    - CELJ - Panel, 2008 (Box 82, Folder 10)
    - CELJ - Reviewer of Journals (Box 83, Folder 1)
    - CELJ - correspondence, August 2005 (Box 83, Folder 2)
    - Center for Scholarly Editions, MLA, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 3)
    - Cole, John - The Center for the Book (Box 83, Folder 4)
    - Conference of College Teachers of English, 1977 (Box 83, Folder 5)
    - Cultural Arts Council, 1986 (Box 83, Folder 6)
    - CUP Proposal, 2008 (Box 83, Folder 7)
    - Curran Awards (folder 1/2) (Box 83, Folder 8)
    - Curran Awards (folder 2/2) (Box 83, Folder 9)
    - Curran Fellowship for Research on the Victorian Press (Box 83, Folder 10)
    - Disciplinary Flashpoints: Conversations Between History and Literature - A Working Conference, April 1-2, 2005 (Box 83, Folder 11)
    - European Romantic Review - Gillray essay, 2009 (Box 83, Folder 12)
    - Fulbright Association, 2006-2008 (Box 83, Folder 13)
    - Guggenheim Project (folder 1/2), 1980-1981 (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Guggenheim Project (folder 2/2), 1980-1981 (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Historians of British Art, c. 1994-1999 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Houston Center for the Humanities (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - The Houston Seminar, May 5, 2005 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - The Houston Seminar, August 2006 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Humanities Texas (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Huxley material (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Inprint, Inc. (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Inprint - The Poets and Writers Ball, 2006 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Interdisciplinary Nineteenth-Century Studies - A Second Annual Colloquium: Revolution, Instability, Change - conference information, April 9-11, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Interdisciplinary Nineteenth-Century Studies - A Second Annual Colloquium: Revolution, Instability, Change - III: Gender and Community, April 9-11, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Interdisciplinary Nineteenth-Century Studies - A Second Annual Colloquium: Revolution, Instability, Change - VIII: Gender and Narrative, April 9-11, 1987 (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Interdisciplinary Nineteenth-Century Studies - A Second Annual Colloquium: Revolution, Instability, Change - X: Images and Archetypes I, April 9-11, 1987 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Interdisciplinary Nineteenth-Century Studies - A Second Annual Colloquium: Revolution, Instability, Change - XII: Social Change and the Novel, April 9-11, 1987 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Interdisciplinary Nineteenth-Century Studies - A Second Annual Colloquium: Revolution, Instability, Change - XIV: Fictions and Poststructuralist Theory, April 9-11, 1987 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Interdisciplinary Nineteenth-Century Studies - A Second Annual Colloquium: Revolution, Instability, Change - XXII: Fiction and Society II, April 9-11, 1987 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Jane Austen Society (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - JSTOR, May 2006 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - JSTOR Participating Publishers meeting, May 14-15, 2007 (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Lehigh University, c. 2008 (Box 85, Folder 8)
    - Listservs - Victoria, SHARP-L, EDITOR-L, 1997-2003 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Mid-west Conference on British Studies, 1977 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - MLA, 2004 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - MLA, 2008 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - MLA Abstracts (folder 1/2), 2007 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - MLA Abstracts (folder 2/2), 2007 (Box 86, Folder 1)
    - MLA bibliography: William D. Schaefer, 1974 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - MLA conference, 2005 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - MLA newsletter, Fall 2010 (Box 86, Folder 4)
    - MLA panel, 1998 (Box 86, Folder 5)
    - MLA Victorian Division (folder 1/2) (Box 86, Folder 6)
    - MLA Victorian Division (folder 2/2) (Box 86, Folder 7)
    - National Endowment for the Humanities (Box 86, Folder 8)
    - National Humanities Center (Box 86, Folder 9)
    - National Research Council, 2006/2007 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Nineteenth-century enquiry group (NICE), 2000-2002 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Nineteenth-century enquiry group (NICE), 2004-2005 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - Nineteenth-century enquiry group (NICE), 2004-2005 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - PEN (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Phi Beta Delta - University of Houston (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Phi Beta Kappa Alumni Association of Greater Houston (folder 1/2) (Box 87, Folder 7)
    - Phi Beta Kappa Alumni Association of Greater Houston (folder 2/2) (Box 87, Folder 8)
    - Phi Beta Kappa - Liberal Arts for a Lifetime, 2005 (Box 87, Folder 9)
    - Phi Beta Kappa Awards, 2002-2003 (Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Phi Beta Kappa lecturer, 2004-2006 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Phi Beta Kappa Senate, 2002-2003 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - Phi Beta Kappa Senate, 2003 (Box 88, Folder 4)
    - Phi Beta Kappa Society and Foundation meetings, Washington DC, December 5-7, 2002 (Box 88, Folder 5)
    - Phi Beta Kappa Texas, 2003-2007 (Box 88, Folder 6)
    - Phi Beta Kappa Texas, 2007-2009 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Phi Beta Kappa Triennial Council, 2000 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - Phi Beta Kappa Triennial, 2003 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Phi Beta Kappa 41st Triennial Council, 2006 (Box 89, Folder 4)
    - Phi Beta Kappa - University of Houston, 2005 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Phi Beta Kappa - UT San Antonio, 2005 (Box 89, Folder 6)
    - Poetry in the Age of the Novel, March 2007 (Box 89, Folder 7)
    - Princeton Alumni Association (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Princeton visiting fellow, 1981-1982 (Box 89, Folder 9)
    - Queen Margaret University, 2008 (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - Ransom Humanities Research Center, 1994-1997 (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - RSVP, 2004-2010 (Box 89, Folder 12)
    - RSVP - Colby Prize, 2006 (Box 90, Folder 1)
    - RSVP - Colby Prize, 2007 (Box 90, Folder 2)
    - The Research Society for Victorian Periodicals presents "Time and the Victorian Press", September 14-16, 2007 (Box 90, Folder 3)
    - St. James Church - every member canvas, 1974 (Box 90, Folder 4)
    - St. James Church - Finance Committee (Box 90, Folder 5)
    - St. James School (Box 90, Folder 6)
    - St. James School fund drive, 1979 (Box 90, Folder 7)
    - Sarofim Seminar (folder 1/2), 2001/2002 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Sarofim Seminar (folder 2/2), 2001/2002 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - Scientia (Box 91, Folder 3)
    - SHARP conference, 1999 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - SHARP conference, 2000 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - SHARP conference - Halifax (folder 1/2), 2005 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - SHARP conference - Halifax (folder 2/2) (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - SHARP conference, 2006-2008 (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - SHARP conference, 2009 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - SHARP conference, 2010 (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - SHARP/JHUP (folder 1/2) (Box 92, Folder 5)
    - SHARP/JHUP (folder 2/2) (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - SHARP proposals, 2004/2005 (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Society of Authors (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Southwestern Alternative Media Project (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Texas A, December 5, 1998 (Box 93, Folder 4)
    - Texas Council for the Humanities, Salado Institute, 1999-2002 (Box 93, Folder 5)
    - Texas Group for the Study of Books and Print Culture (Box 93, Folder 6)
    - Tex(t)net (Box 93, Folder 7)
    - Tex(t)net Workshop - Ransom Center, 2006 (Box 93, Folder 8)
    - University of California Press (Box 93, Folder 9)
    - Victorian Counter Culture Conference, 1974 (Box 93, Folder 10)
    - Victorian Division panel, 2008 (Box 93, Folder 11)
    - Victorians Institute Conference - The Citadel, Charleston SC, October 4-5, 2002 (Box 93, Folder 12)
    - Victorian Literature and Culture (Box 93, Folder 13)
    - Victorian Society of America (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Victorian Studies (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - Subseries F: Scholarship
    - "Afterword" - Colorado County Photographs - Patsy Craven, 1998 (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - "Beyond Vocational Training: Liberal Arts as a Lifetime Degree" - Phi Beta Kappa, St. Mary's University, 2005 (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - "Beyond Vocational Training: Liberal Arts as a Lifetime Degree" - Phi Beta Kappa, University of St. Thomas, 2004 (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - "Beyond Vocational Training: Liberal Arts for a Lifetime" - Phi Beta Kappa, Colorado State University, 2005 (Box 94, Folder 6)
    - Cambridge History of the Book in Britain - The Serial Revolution (folder 1/3) (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - Cambridge History of the Book in Britain - The Serial Revolution (folder 2/3) (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - Cambridge History of the Book in Britain - The Serial Revolution (folder 3/3) (Box 94, Folder 9)
    - Christ Church Cathedral - Religion and Arts Council (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - "Collaborationa and Copyright" - Victorian Collaboration Conference, CUNY, 1998 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - Dictionary of National Biography, 1998-2001 (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - Dictionary of National Biography - Bentley (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - Dictionary of National Biography - Bentley, George (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Dictionary of National Biography - Bentley, Richard (folder 1/2) (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Dictionary of National Biography - Bentley, Richard (folder 2/2) (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Dictionary of National Biography - Bentley, Samuel (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Dictionary of National Biography - Bogue, David (Box 95, Folder 9)
    - Dictionary of National Biography - Bradbury, Henry Riley (Box 95, Folder 10)
    - Dictionary of National Biography - Bradbury, William (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Dictionary of National Biography - Bradbury, William Hardwick (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - Dictionary of National Biography - Browne, Hablot Knight (folder 1/3) (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Dictionary of National Biography - Browne, Hablot Knight (folder 2/3) (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Dictionary of National Biography - Browne, Hablot Knight (folder 3/3) (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Dictionary of National Biography - Buss, Robert William (Box 96, Folder 6)
    - Dictionary of National Biography - Chapman, Edward (Box 96, Folder 7)
    - Dictionary of National Biography - Chapman, Frederic (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - Dictionary of National Biography - Cruikshank, George (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Dictionary of National Biography - Cruikshank, Isaac (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Dictionary of National Biography - Cruikshank, (Isaac) Robert (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Dictionary of National Biography - Evans, Frederick Moule (Box 97, Folder 5)
    - Dictionary of National Biography - Evans, Frederick Mullet (Box 97, Folder 6)
    - Dictionary of National Biography - Macrone, John (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Dictionary of National Biography - Meadows, Joseph Kenny (Box 97, Folder 8)
    - Dictionary of National Biography - Merle, William Henry (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Dictionary of National Biography - Sibson, Thomas (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Dictionary of National Biography - Smeeton, George (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Dictionary of National Biography - Stone, Frank (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - The Edinburgh History of the Book in Scotland (folder 1/2) (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - The Edinburgh History of the Book in Scotland (folder 2/2) (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Editing Blackwood's (folder 1/4) (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Editing Blackwood's (folder 2/4) (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Editing Blackwood's (folder 3/4) (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Editing Blackwood's (folder 4/4) (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - The English Country Cottage, 2005 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Editopia 2001: A Fantasy - CELJ, Keynote, MLA, 1998 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - From Home to Square Street: Narrative Traversals, 2001 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Health Care and the Arts Lecture Series - Helen, A Bipolar Journey, 2003 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - History of the Book in Canada (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Imagination on a Long Run - English Literature Illustrated (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - In the Pit's Much Mire: From Waste to Art - Museum of Fine Arts Houston/Rice School of Continuing Studies (folder 1/2), 1998 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - In the Pit's Much Mire: From Waste to Art - Museum of Fine Arts Houston/Rice School of Continuing Studies (folder 2/2) (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - The Insides and Outsides of Waverly - Material Cultures: The Book, the Text, and the Archive, July 29-30, 2000 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Literature in the Market Place - preface (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - Matters of Material Interest - Victorian Literature and Culture, 2007 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Novel, untitled, undated (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Out Bodies/Closeted Minds - SCMLA, 1998 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Patten biographies/reviews findings (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Perspectival Structure in the Novel (Swarthmore thesis), 1960 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - The Politics of Humor in George Cruikshank's Graphic Satire - Adler Lecture, Catherine Golden correspondence (folder 1/4) (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - The Politics of Humor in George Cruikshank's Graphic Satire - Adler Lecture, Catherine Golden correspondence (folder 2/4) (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - The Politics of Humor in George Cruikshank's Graphic Satire - Adler Lecture, Catherine Golden correspondence (folder 3/4) (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - The Politics of Humor in George Cruikshank's Graphic Satire - Adler Lecture, Catherine Golden correspondence (folder 4/4) (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Rembrandt - Harry Berger, Jr. (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Should Fairytales be Censored - Rienzi, February 2011 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Signifying Shape (folder 1/2) (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Signifying Shape (folder 2/2) (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Squadrons of Satirists; or, the Canyons of Caricature: The War-Time Weapons of Humor - Museum of Fine Arts Houston, March 19, 2009 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Taking Tennyson's Serial Poem Serially - RSVP (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Victorian Institute conference - Loyal to the Royal: Tennyson Refigures Victoria, Fall 2007 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Victorian Institute conference - Textualizing War, October 2002 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Victorian Poetry essay - The Contemporaneity of the Last Tournament (folder 1/2) (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Victorian Poetry essay - The Contemporaneity of the Last Tournament (folder 2/2) (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - The Victorians - Phi Beta Kappa, 2003 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - What is the History of the Book - Alumni College lecture, 1998 (Box 103, Folder 2)
  - Subseries G: Dickens Scholarship
    - 101st International Conference of the Dickens Fellowship - Dickens Collected Articles, 2007 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Bleak House essay, 2005/2006 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Bleak House - "London" (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - "Blurb" for Other Dickens by John Bowen (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Buzfuz (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Cerisy catalog and talk (folder 1/2), 2011 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Cerisy catalog and talk (folder 2/2), 2011 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Dickens - collected articles (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Dickens commentary (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Dickens Companion: The Christmas Books (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Dickens Fellowship (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Dickens House - London (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Dickens Listserv (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Dickens publication (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Dickens Society - Nominating Committee (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Dickens Society - research (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Dickens - Strand/Museum (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Dickens Studies Annual (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Dickens Symposium (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Dickens Universe / SHARP conference, 2001 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - English Studies Review, 2009 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Friends of the Charles Dickens Museum (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Friends of Fondren Library - What's Victorian about Christmas, December 2010 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - From Sketches to Nickleby: The Author Discovers His Vocation - John Jordan (folder 1/2), 1999 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - From Sketches to Nickleby: The Author Discovers His Vocation - John Jordan (folder 2/2) (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - John, Juliet - Dickens' Villains Reviews (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - MLA - Bleak House, 2007 (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - MLA - Dickens (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Museum of Fine Arts - Christmas, 1998 (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Nineteenth Century Contexts (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Oxford Dickens Companions (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Palgrave Advances in Charles Dickens Studies - proofs (folder 1/2), 2005 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Palgrave Advances in Charles Dickens Studies - proofs (folder 1/2), 2005 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - SHARP conference - Anon, Boz, Charles Dickens: The ABCDs of Authorship, 2003 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - What and Where is London in Bleak House (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Phizzing - Princeton (folder 1/3) (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Phizzing - Princeton (folder 2/3) (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Phizzing - Princeton (folder 3/3) (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - United Presbyterian Church lecture, 2004 (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Dickens Project (Box 108)
    - Dickens Project (folder 1/4) (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Dickens Project (folder 2/4) (Box 107, Folder 5)
    - Dickens Project (folder 3/4) (Box 107, Folder 6)
    - Dickens Project (folder 4/4) (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Dickens Project, August 2007 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Dickens Project, Winter 2007 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Dickens Project, Winter 2011 (Box 108, Folder 4)
    - Dickens Project funding (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Dickens Project - London - University of California Santa Cruz, August 1, 2001 (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Dickens Project papers (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Dickens Project winter conference - University of California Riverside, February 21-23, 1992 (Box 109, Folder 1)
  - Subseries H: Academic Journals/Newsletters/Publicatons
    - ADE Bulletin, Winter, Spring, Fall 2000 (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Blackwell's, 1974-1978 (Box 109, Folder 3)
    - Beverly Hills High Lights - Alumni Highlights, Hall of Fame Who's Who, Summer 2002 (Box 109, Folder 4)
    - Censorship - Centre to Centre newsletter of the Writers in Prison committee of International PEN, 1994-1997 (Box 109, Folder 5)
    - Censorship - International PEN Writers in Prison committee (Box 109, Folder 6)
    - A Guide to the Archives of the Cambridge University Press, 1973 (Box 109, Folder 7)
    - Grafton essay - The New Yorker, November 5, 2007 (Box 109, Folder 8)
    - Houston Grand Opera - A History (Box 109, Folder 9)
    - The Key Reporter - Phi Beta Kappa, Fall 2005 (Box 109, Folder 10)
    - The PEN Newsletter, 1995, 1997 (Box 109, Folder 11)
    - Reading Experience Database (Box 109, Folder 12)
    - The Strand Magazine, 2006 (Box 110, Folder 1)
    - Th Texas Humanist, March 1979 (Box 110, Folder 2)
    - Texas Journal of Ideas, History and Culture, Fall 1986 (Box 110, Folder 3)
    - Victorian Studies Bulletin, volumes 13-30, incomplete, c. 1989-2006 (Box 110, Folder 4)
    - Book - A Directory of Woodrow Wilson Fellows, 1968 (Box 110)
    - Book - English Book Illustration in the European Context (2 copies), 1990 (Box 110)
    - Journal - Feminist Economics (v. 4 no. 2), Summer 1998 (Box 110)
    - Journal - Representations 42, Spring 1993 (Box 110)
      - Book - The Peace Library Centennial, 2004 (Box 110)
  - Subseries I: Oversize Materials and Other Media
    - Oversize Materials and Other Media, DeGruttola Award, Books, Personal, Rice-Related, Other Media (Box 111)
  - Subseries J: Dickens Scholarship, Correspondence, and Student Work
    - "Serial Illustrations and Storytelling in David Copperfield" (1/3) (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - "Serial Illustrations and Storytelling in David Copperfield" (2/3) (Box 112, Folder 2)